24小时
第三季  第三集
前情提要
如果我能拿到基勒的剧本呢?
What if I can get us a copy of keeler's playbook?
什么是"剧本"?
What exactly do you mean by "playbook"?
今晚辩论的所有预稿
His entire prep for tonight's debate.
-见鬼 叫你别这么干  -听我说?
-Damn it, I told you to drop that.  -Will you just listen to me?
有些内容你需要看一下
There is something you need to see.
没什么我需要看的
There's nothing I need to see.
关于安妮的 我们所不知道的她
It's about anne. It's something that we didn't know about her.
这会毁掉我们大家
Something that could damage all of us.
-现在能和你谈谈吗?  -当然
-Can I talk to you now?  -Yeah, Of course.
金 什么事?
Kim, what's up?
蔡斯和我交往一段时间了
Chase and I have been going out for a while,
我们是认真的
and it's starting to get serious.
我很在乎他 爸
I really care for him, dad.
-你怎么看?  -我不知道
-So what do you think?  -I don't know what I think.
释放拉姆·萨拉扎
We want the release of Ramon Salazar.
如果你们拒绝
If you refuse to comply,
我们就散播病毒
the virus will be released.
病毒被做成了晶体状
It looks like the virus was delivered in a crystalline form.
也许病毒就在白粉中
Maybe what you're looking for is a white powder.
比如一包可卡因 或海洛因?
It would look like a bag of cocaine or heroin?
对 也许这是他们的诡计 毒贩以为自己在卖毒品
Yeah, that may even be the strategy. Someone thinks they're selling a bag of coke.
实则是在传播病毒
when, in fact, they're handling the virus.
-你哪儿来的钱  -这不重要
-Where did you get that money  -It doesn't matter.
我们需要这钱
Okay, we needed it.
于是我弄到了钱
I got it.
你就这样帮助家里人?
So this is how you're going to help you're family?
贩毒?
By dealing drugs?
不是贩毒 只是运送
I'm not dealing them. It's a stupid delivery.
那孩子带着一包有病毒的毒品倒处走
That kid's walking around with a bag of cocaine that's got the virus in it.
而毫不知情
He doesn't know it.
我要找到他 阻止毒品散播
I need to find him and stop him from putting it into circulation.
你没注射毒品吧?
You didn't shoot up, did you?
怎么? 你以为瞒得住我?
Why? You think you can hide it?
我不是想瞒你
I'm not trying to hide it from you.
-我是想戒掉  -戒掉还不够 杰克
-I'm trying to quit.  -Okay. People don't just quit, Jack.
我不想
I am not
留下毒瘾记录 懂吗?
going on record with this addiction. Do you understand me?
你是唯一知道此事的人 不要告诉别人
You're the only person who knows about it, so it's going to stay that way.
给我最新情报
Give me an update.
凯尔还在家里
Kyle's still in his house.
货呢?
What about the package?
在他手上
It's with him.
-拉姆呢?  -等着回家呢
-And Ramon?  -Just waiting to come home.
很好
Good.
亚当 下载大家的会议文件夹了吗?
Adam, have you downloaded everyone's folders for the meeting?
还没 我还在追踪病毒的详细资料
Not yet. I'm still pulling up some of the medical details about the virus.
别在那上面花太多时间
Don't waste a lot of time on that.
我们只需要知道症状出现24小时内会要人命
The only thing our people need to know is that it kills within 24 hours of exposure
还有它正在凯尔 辛格勒手上
and we believe Kyle Singer is transporting it.
知道了
I got all that.
-找到辛格勒了吗?  -杰克要去找妮可·邓肯
-What about our approach to Singer?  -Jack's going to meet Nicole Duncan,
洛杉矶卫生局长
head of health services, Los Angeles.
他们会带防疫组去辛格勒家
They're going to take a haz-mat team over to Singer's apartment.
他正在等她
He's waiting for her now.
嗨 杰克
Hi, Jack.
你好吗?
How you doing?
我很好 妮可 你呢?
I'm okay, Nicole. How have you been?
今天中午前还挺好
Until this afternoon, I was doing fine.
呃 我...
You know, I, uh...
听说特里的事后 我联系过你
I tried to reach you after I heard about Teri.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
那事之后 我是很消沉
After that, I kind of withdrew.
谢谢你打电话给我
But I appreciated the calls. Thanks.
我们走吧
We should get going.
我刚运行完马切尔的流行病估测分析程序
I just finished running Macer's epidemiological model.
她的估计不对
Her estimates were off.
比先前预计的好还是坏?
Better or worse than we thought?
比以前坏两倍
Twice as bad.
她估计一周后9%的人口会被感染
She had nine percent of the population infected within a week,
但几乎会达到20%
but it's closer to 20%.
致死性比她预计的更高
And the infection-to-mortality rate is higher than her estimate.
达到95%
Almost 95% lethal.
我追踪细菌12年了 从没见过这样可怕的
I've been hunting germs for 12 years and I've never seen anything like this.
嗯
Great.
你没事吧?
Are you feeling okay?
没事 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
你在流汗
You're perspiring.
我中午起就没休息过
I've been non-stop since noon.
听着 我们还有8分钟时间
Look, we're going to be about eight minutes out.
我们到之前 你再翻翻防疫协约吧
It would be great if we could go over the quarantine protocols before we get there.
-好的  -嗯
-No problem.  -Good.
如果你们拒绝 我们就散播病毒
If you refuse to comply, the virus will be released.
释放拉姆·萨拉扎...
I want the release of Ramon Salazar...
盖尔.
Gael
来看看这个
Here, take a look at this.
快查到电话的来源了
Closing in on the point of origin of this call.
看到这个伪造的编码了吗?
You see this code artifact here?
-嗯  -我有新发现
-Yeah.  -I found a few more on this recording.
我相信它来自国内通信中转点
I think it's coming from a domestic switching node.
你认为电话是在美国境内打的?
You think the call was made from inside the U.S.?
有可能 我把它传到你的系统
Maybe. I'm piping it over to your system.
你查一下有没有符合的
See if you can find a match.
-好  -开完会再做吧
-Okay.  -But do it after the meeting.
什么会?
What meeting?
托尼会做些资源调动 以帮助杰克的行动
Tony's shifting resources to help Jack in the field.
他快找到病毒了
He's closing in on the virus.
-盖尔  -嗯?
-Gael.  -Yeah?
在杰克到辛格勒家前 把声音系统调整好
Jack needs that audio feed in place when he gets to Kyle Singer's apartment.
我知道 但托尼要我现在做些别的事
I know, but Tony needs me to take care of something right now.
-开完会我再帮你  -我需要你开会前做
-I'll get it to you after the meeting.  -I need you to do it before the meeting.
杰克正在路上 现在就去做
Jack's on his way there. So come do it now.
不行! 别烦我
I can't! Stop bugging me.
我会帮你的
I'll get it to you.
好吧
Fine.
你觉得拉姆回来后会怎样?
Have you thought about how it will be when Ramon comes back?
会怎样?
How it will be?
像以前一样啊
Like it was before.
情况不一样了 赫克托
Things have changed, Hector.
没什么不一样
Nothing's changed.
他才走了三个月
He's only been gone three months.
你不一样了
You've changed.
他进了监狱 你就是头儿
You've been in charge while he's been in prison.
你想这么轻易放弃?
Are you willing to give that up so easily?
什么事?
What is it?
鲍尔就快截获我们的货了
Bauer's telling CTU he's about to intercept the package.
-怎么会?  -不知道 我正在查
-How?  -I'm not sure. I'm about to find out.
-货还在凯尔 辛格勒手上?  -当然
-Is Gomez still on Kyle Singer?  -Of course.
那就好
Then we're fine.
喂 面试如何?
Hey, how was the interview?
不错
Fine.
怎么了 爸?
What's up, dad?
你妈说你付清了
Your mother told me you paid the rent.
我们欠下的三个月房租
All three months we owed.
是 我赚了点钱
Yeah. I came into a little money.
一个没工作的19岁男孩怎么赚钱?
How does a 19-year-old kid who doesn't have a job come into a little money?
蒂姆和我 前天去赌马
Tim and I, we went down to the track the other day.
他在马厩有内线
He knows this guy over at the stables, so, uh,
-所以我们赚了一笔  -你从哪儿来的钱?
-we got a tip.  -Where did you get the money?
爸 这很重要吗?
Dad, what does it matter?
老实话 付了三个月房租
Honestly, the rent's paid for three months. All right?
我们现在没压力了
The pressure's off us now.
你干了非法的勾当?
Did you do something illegal?
没有
No.
我们去了圣阿尼塔
I told you we went to Santa Anita,
我们运气好 我没干非法的事
and we got lucky. I didn't do anything illegal.
别撒谎 我操的心已经够多了
Don't lie to me. I've got enough to worry about.
我是当家的
Now, this is my house.
我付房租! 我照顾你和你妈妈
I pay the rent! I take care of you and your mother.
等你找到工作
And when you get that job,
你再来当家 还我的钱 好吗?
you go ahead and pay me back, huh?
别走 我们还没谈完!
Wait a second. We're not done here!
谈完了
No, we're done here.
别跑!
Don't walk away from me!
你应该谢谢我 而不是在这里指责我
You should be thanking me instead of crawling up my ass.
凯尔!
Kyle!
开门!
Open the door!
他叫凯尔 辛格勒
His name's Kyle Singer.
我们认为他正在转运病毒
We think he's transporting the virus,
但他并不知道自己手上真正是什么
although it's likely he doesn't realize what he's carrying.
他怎么会不知道?
How could he not know?
卫生部相信 病毒被做成海洛因或可卡因的样子
Health Services believes that the virus was made to look like heroin or cocaine.
我们了解到凯尔 辛格勒受雇 将毒品从墨西哥带给洛杉矶一毒贩
We know that Kyle Singer was hired to deliver a package from Mexico to a dealer in LA.
他以为自己在走私毒品
He thinks he's smuggling drugs.
这就是他们的诡计
That's the working theory.
我们的问题是 辛格勒送交了毒品后
Now, here's the thing. Once Singer delivers that bag of powder,
病毒会被打开 然后在城市中传播
it gets cut up and distributed throughout the city.
那时候 一切就失控了
At that point, it becomes impossible to contain.
洛杉矶警局抓住辛格勒了吗?
Was LAPD grabbing Singer?
没有
No.
啊? 他们就不能再快点吗?
Why not? Can't they get there faster?
洛杉矶警局并不知晓 如何处理防疫区
LAPD is not trained to handle haz-zone.
杰克·鲍尔会和一组卫生部的人一起去
Jack Bauer's going to go in with a team from Health Services.
我们在这里进行协助
We're going to run the operation from here,
并及时通知总统
updating the president in real time.
现在
Now,
我们得小心地接近辛格勒
we have to approach Singer with care.
他并不知道那包粉有多可怕
He has no idea how deadly this powder is.
我没骂他 只是问了他些问题
I'm not fighting. I'm just asking the questions.
-他应该尊重我们  -是的...
-He should respect us.  -Of course he does...
你冷静一下吧?
now will you please calm down?
1千8百美元...
$1,800 is...
他说赌马赢的钱?
He said he won the money at the track?
真是说谎不打草稿
He could come up with a better lie than that.
也许他说的是真的
Well, maybe he's telling the truth.
得了吧 海伦
Oh, come on, Helen.
-你去哪儿?  -随便
-Where you going?  -Wherever.
包里是什么?
What's in the bag?
-衣服  -打开看下
-Some clothes.  -Well, open it.
什么?
What?
把包打开
Open the bag.
警告你: 把包打开
I'm warning you: Open that bag
不然我自己来
or I'm going to open it myself.
妈?
Mom?
-凯尔 听爸的话  -这不关他的事
-Kyle, listen to your father.  -It's none of his business.
这是我家 就得听我的!
As long as you're living in my house, it is!
你家?
Your house?
这不是你家 你连房租都付不起
This isn't your house. You can't even pay the rent.
别 凯尔...
Oh, Kyle...
拜托 这是我的隐私 求你了?
Come on, will you quit snooping, please?
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
这是什么? 嗯?
What is this? Huh?
可卡因? 海洛因?
Coke? Heroin?
-还给我 爸  -你说什么?
-Give it back, dad.  -What did you say?
-我需要它  -"需要"是什么意思?
-I need it.  -What do you mean, you "need" it?
你在吸毒?
What are you, some kind of junkie?
没有
No.
我只是把它交给某个人? 如果没办到的话...
I'm just delivering it to this guy, okay? And if I don't get it to him...
谁?
Who?
-某个人而已?  -他是谁?!
-It's just a guy, okay?  -Who?!
他叫什么名字
Give me a name.
凯尔 回答你爸
Kyle, answer your father.
还给我 好吗?!
You just give it to me, okay?!
别这样! 别这样 你们两个!
Stop it! Hey, stop it, both of you!
你们俩! 别这样!
Both of you! Both of you!
住手! 山姆! 住手 山姆!
Stop! Sam! Sam, don't, Sam!
凯尔!
Kyle!
我只说一遍
I can't reiterate this enough.
这是场真正的威胁
This is a credible threat.
如果我们不快一步 萨拉扎的人就会散播病毒
Salazar's people will release this virus if we don't find it first.
大家开工吧
So lets get going.
我们需要一间绝尘室 有摄相和收音系统
Okay, we're going to need a white room with full audio and video capability.
准备好后通知我
Get me 3b if that's available.
让疑犯签字 我马上过去
Log him in. I'll be there in a minute.
你不是应该和我爸在一起吗
I thought you were supposed to be with my dad.
本来是 但他派我回来
I was. He sent me back here.
为什么?
Why?
审问帕克
To question Parker.
帕克? 他已经供出了凯尔 辛格勒 还有什么好问的?
Parker? He already turned in Kyle Singer. What else are you going to get from him?
对
Nothing.
这就是问题所在
And that's the point.
-我不明白  -你爸让我坐冷板凳 金
-I don't understand. -Your dad's sidelining me, Kim.
他不让我参与行动
He's making me sit out.
为什么?
Why?
你说呢?
Why do you think?
因为我俩的关系?
Because of us?
-蔡斯 抱歉...  -他说他在保护我...
-Chase, I'm sorry...  -He says he's protecting me...
但我不是需要他保护的人
but I'm not the one he's trying to protect here.
你在怪我?
You're not blaming me, are you?
我的意思是 我们还不该告诉他
Look, all I'm saying is, we shouldn't have told him.
那我们该怎么办?
What were we supposed to do?
一直地下情 直到被人发现?
Keep sneaking around until someone catches us?
我们可以再等等
We could have waited.
等到什么时候?
Until when?
不管什么时候告诉他 都是一样的结果
He'd have the same response no matter when we told him.
我要去审帕克这小子了
I got to deal with this kid Parker.
杰弗里
Jeffery.
今天的饭烂透了
The food's exceptionally bad today.
这个国家哪条法律规定
Aren't there laws in this country
使用残忍和不人道的惩罚?
for cruel and unusual punishment?
告诉安尼康 我有话要说
Tell Annicon, I'm ready to talk.
鲍尔没告诉我 但萨拉扎确实有些手段
Bauer couldn't tell me, but Salazar's got some kind of leverage.
能让他得到释放
Enough to get him released.
我不会让这杂种 浪费我两年的努力
I'm not about to let this son of a bitch erase the last two years of my life.
打给你在国防部的朋友 看能得到什么消息
Call your friend at the state department, see what he can tell you.
我是安尼康
Annicon.
-安尼康先生?  -嗯
-Mr. Annicon?  -Yeah.
我是杰夫•本森 是萨拉扎的看守
This is Jeff Benson, Salazar's guard.
我知道你
I know who you are.
先生 萨拉扎要见你
Sir, Salazar asked to see you.
为什么?
Why?
他有话要跟你说
He says he's ready to talk.
我马上来
I'll be right there.
别问我原因 照办就行
Don't ask me why, just do it.
我希望你能拿到退款
I hope you can get a refund.
退款?
A refund?
让卖这份垃圾给你的人退款
From whoever sold you that load of crap.
大卫,
David
基勒会用这个在辩论中攻击你
Keeler is going to use this against you in this debate.
无视它对你没有任何好处
Now, ignoring it's not going to make it go away.
做出回应也不会显得更高贵
Neither will dignifying it with a response.
他会指出安妮曾经做过伪证 别忘了
He's going to claim that Anne perjured herself, which, in case you've forgotten,
-做伪证是大罪  -安妮没犯罪
-is a felony.  -Anne is no felon.
这句话足以毁了你
The allegation itself is enough to damage you.
好了 大卫 请想一想
Now, come on, David please, think.
你知道要参加这辩论 不能不做回应
You know you can't go into this debate without some kind of response.
你想怎么办?
What do you propose?
和安妮谈谈
Talk to Anne,
让她告诉你一切
make sure she's told you everything.
她已经告诉我一切了
She has told me everything.
是吗?
Are you sure?
我和安妮交往以来
Ever since I started seeing Anne,
你老是抓住机会 破坏我们的关系
you've taken every chance to undermine our relationship.
-因为你不喜欢她...  -是的 我不喜欢她
-Just because you don't like her...  -You're absolutely right, I don't like her.
这不是我和安妮之间的事 是你和安妮的事
This isn't about me and Anne. It's about you and Anne.
如果她没有隐瞒任何事 那很好 她也不必隐瞒
Now, if she's got nothing to hide, fine, David, she's got nothing to hide.
你得在与基勒的电视辩论前 查清楚
But you'd better find out before you face off with Keeler on national television.
问过你朋友杰克·鲍尔发生什么事了吗?
Did you ask your friend Jack Bauer what's going on?
你问了 是吗?
You did, didn't you?
但他不会说
But he wouldn't say.
很不爽吧 路易斯 被蒙在鼓里
Must be very frustrating, Luis, being kept in the dark.
你有什么要说的?
You have something to tell me?
-你还没回答我?  -有屁快放
-I asked you here, didn't I?  -Then start talking,
一小时前 我的耐性就用光了
because you used up my patience an hour ago.
你真是只叨着骨头的狗 路易斯
you are dog with a bone, Luis.
一旦咬住了 就不肯放
Once you bite down, you don't let go.
我出去后
When I'm out of here,
我不希望看见你又咬住我
I don't want you on me anymore.
你什么时候出去?
When you're out of here?
问得好
You were right.
几小时后 我就能回家了
In a few hours, I'm going home.
真的?
Really?
你怎么做到的?
And how will you manage that?
赫克托是个好兄弟
Hector's a good brother.
除非他有监狱的钥匙
Unless he's got a key to this place,
-否则你哪都别想去  -他就是有钥匙
-you're not going anywhere.  -But he does have a key.
当他拧动钥匙
And when he turns it,
你这两年的时间
the last two years of your life,
疏忽自己家人的时间
all the hours you've spent away from your family,
为了抓我所做的一切努力
all the work you've done to put me in here
都会白费...
will go away...
... 像这样
... just like that.
我就是想说这些给你听 路易斯
I wanted you to hear it from me, Luis.
这会是你最后听到的话
I wanted it to be the last thing you ever heard.
你很快就能见到你儿子了
Your son will be returned to you now.
我觉得凯尔肯定有问题
I'm just saying that Kyle is in over his head.
我们不用请律师
We're not calling a lawyer.
-他还没被捕  -暂时没有
-He hasn't even been arrested.  -Not yet.
也许他不会被捕
Maybe he won't be.
如果我们不要管这事
If we leave it alone, don't do anything,
事情可能很快就会结束了
maybe this whole thing will just go away.
-你不认真的吧  -我是认真的 山姆?
-You can't be serious.  -Why not, Sam?
为什么要搞得人尽皆知?
Why do we have to let anybody know?
-因为这是违法的  -那你要我怎么做
-Because it's against the law not to.  -What are you suggesting we do,
叫警察?
call the police?
我们再用举报奖金付房租
Maybe they'll give us a reward and then we can pay our rent.
不能这样做
All right, that wasn't fair.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
上帝啊!
Oh, my god!
-你在干嘛?  -甩掉这玩意儿!
-Hey, what are you doing?  -I'm going to get rid of it!
-你要送儿子进监狱?!  -等待
-You want to visit your son in jail?!  -Wait a minute.
海伦!
Helen!
-后退! 后退!  -你们是什么人?
-Get back! Get back!  -Who are you people?
凯尔 辛格勒在哪儿?!
Where's Kyle Singer?!
-凯尔 辛格勒!  -他不在
-Kyle Singer!  -He's not here.
把他隔离 做全面血检 拿棉签来
Isolate him and draw blood for a full panel. Get an oral swab.
封死所有窗户和通风口
Seal off all these windows and vents.
不!
No!
在这儿! 在这儿!
In here! In here!
-不!  -隔离她
-No!  -Put her in quarantine.
托尼 病毒散出去了
Tony, the virus is out.
重复 病毒散出去了
I repeat, the virus is out.
收到 杰克 在哪儿?
Copy that, Jack. Where is it?
污水处理系统
In the sewage system.
通知污水局关闭底下水系统
Get DWP to shut down the lines from ground zero.
也可能散播到空气中了
It might also be airborne.
让消防局和警局安设隔离墙
Get the fire department and LAPD to set up a perimeter.
通知他们这里是三级疫区
Tell them we've got a level-three hot zone.
收到
Copy that.
请进
Come in.
韦恩说你想见我
Wayne said you wanted to see me.
什么事?
What's wrong?
基勒.
Keeler
会在辩论中提及你前夫
He's bringing your ex-husband into this debate.
证监会对他公司的调查
The SEC's investigation into his company.
嗯 泰德被判有罪 正在服刑
Well, Ted was convicted, and served his sentence.
你知道的
You know that.
你告诉过我的
I know what you told me.
我把所有的事都告诉你了
I told you everything there is to know.
泰德的公司引进了一种高血压药...
Ted's company was introducing a hypertension drug...
-你审过检验报告  -对
-and you reviewed the research.  -Yes.
结果证实报告是捏造的
Which later turned out to have been fabricated.
泰德知道是假的
Which Ted knew at the time,
但我不知道
and I didn't.
现在泰德又称你也知道
Now Ted's claiming that you both knew.
他不能推翻自己8年前的证词
He can't reverse himself 8 years after giving sworn testimony.
他做了
Well, he is.
他会在记者会上公开说明
And he's willing to go on record with the press.
我只能说 他在说谎
I don't know what to say, except he's a liar.
你说的和他的不一致
It's your word against his.
大卫...
David...
你有理由怀疑我
you have reason to be suspicious.
上帝明白
God knows,
你曾被最信任的人被叛过
you've been betrayed by some of the people you've trusted most,
但我不是雪莉
but I'm not Sherry.
事实我已说过一次
I told you the whole truth once.
我不会过多解释
I'm not going to defend it.
因为没什么比你我之间的信任更重要...
Because if there's anything less than complete trust between us...
我相信你 安妮
I do trust you, Anne.
你应该相信我
You should.
喂
Yes.
我们得谈谈 大卫 我和安妮正在谈
We need to talk, David. I'm with Anne now.
我猜她全盘否认了
Ah, let me guess she denied everything.
我相信她
I believe her.
听着 我有办法处理这些事
Yeah, well, listen, I might be able to make this whole thing go away.
怎么做?
How?
礼堂见面再谈...
Meet you in the auditorium...
单独
alone.
好吧
All right.
你有时间看妮可写的行动报告了吗?
So have you had a chance to take a look at Nicole's field report yet?
嗯 快看完了
Yeah. I'm almost done.
有什么看法?
What are your impressions?
从我读到的内容看 比较乐观
Based on what I've read so far, I'm optimistic.
你是说我们能够控制病毒?
So you think we'll be able to contain the virus?
至少可以控制受害者人数
At the very least, we should be able to limit the casualties.
但病毒散布到空中了啊?
Even though the virus was airborne?
虽然有传播的危险 但妮可的小组反应迅速
Well, there is some risk of it spreading, but Nicole's team acted fast.
他们疏散并封锁了那栋楼 并隔离了辛格勒一家
They evacuated and sealed off the apartment building and quarantined the Singers.
-什么时候出化验结果?  -5分钟 最多10分钟
-When do we get the test results?  -Five minutes, ten tops.
看来运气不错啊?
So looks like we lucked out, huh?
-是该有点运气  -很好 听着
-Yeah, we deserve a little luck.  -All right, look,
我要挂了 有消息随时通知我 好吗?
I got to go. Make sure you keep me in the loop, all right?
-好的 你也一样  -好的
-Okay, you do the Same.  -Okay.
托尼 警局已经设了隔离区 他们要知道刚才15分钟的风向
Tony, LAPD's setting up the perimeter, but they need wind vectors for the last 15 minutes.
打给气象局
Call meteorology.
212号分机
Extension 212.
托尼 媒体知道了被抛在卫生部外的
Tony, local news picked up the story about the dead body
那具尸体
being dumped at Health Services.
哦
Great.
他们要听解释 我该怎么说?
They want a statement. What do you want me to tell them?
啥都别说
Nothing.
托尼 有个叫典狱官 米切尔的打电话找你
Tony, Warden Mitchell is on the phone.
从监狱打来 说是急事
He's calling from the prison. He says it's urgent.
我是阿尔梅达
Almeida.
辛格勒先生 辛格勒夫人?
Mr. and Mrs. Singer?
倒底出了什么事?
What the hell is going on here?
跟毒品又没关系
Because this is not about drugs.
你们可能感染了一种病毒
We think you've been exposed to a virus.
-病毒?  -叫做科迪勒拉病毒
-A virus?  -It's called Cordillera Virus.
你们儿子今早偷将病毒 从墨西哥携带入境
We believe that your son carried it in from Mexico this morning without knowing.
"携带"怎么讲? 怎么会?
What do you mean "carried it in"? How?
他以为自己在运送毒品
He thought he was carrying drugs.
我们被感染了?
So, we've been exposed?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
有什么后果? 我们安全吗?
Wh... what does that mean? Are we sick?
检验结果出来前 你们将被隔离
We're going to have to keep you quarantined until we get the results back from your tests.
抱歉
Excuse me for one moment.
-喂 我是鲍尔  -杰克 我是托尼
-Yeah, this is Bauer.  -Jack, it's Tony.
托尼 我认为凯尔 辛格勒被感染了
Tony, I think Kyle Singer's been exposed.
好 我们已集中全力在他身上
Yeah, we've already got an all points out on him.
你们设好隔离区了吗?
Have you set a perimeter?
我们正尽全力控制事态
Yeah. We're doing everything we can to contain this thing.
所有探员和部门 组成了高度机密的智囊团队
All agencies and departments are in the loop on a need-to-know basis.
-干得好  -杰克 听着
-Okay, good work.  -Listen, Jack,
本不该现在告诉你 但
I know this isn't a best time to tell you, but
收到坏消息 你一定想知道
I just got some bad news. I figured you'd want to know about it.
什么事?
What's wrong?
路易斯 安尼康被杀了
Luis Annicon was murdered.
-被杀 怎么会?  -萨拉扎的看守干的
-Murdered, how?  -Salazar's guard.
我们扣押了他 他说...
We've got him in custody. He claims that ...
萨拉扎绑架了他儿子 如果不这样做就撕票
Salazar had a son kidnapped and threatened to kill him if he didn't do it.
杰克 很抱歉 我知道你俩为了查案曾紧密合作
Jack, I'm sorry. I know you two worked closely on this case.
-托尼 我马上回来  -没事吧?
-Tony, I'm going to have to get back to you.  -Is everything okay?
-我马上回来  -杰克?
-I'm going to get back to you.  -Jack?
-结果不对吧  -是对的
-These results can't be right.  -They are.
-再查一次  -查过了
-Check it again.  -I have.
血液和唾液 空气和体表 都呈阴性
Blood and saliva, atmospheric and surface tests, they're all negative.
一点病毒的痕迹都没发现
We can't find even a... a trace amount of this virus.
你在干嘛? 你还没冲洗消毒呢
What the hell are you doing? You haven't showered down yet.
-没危险了  -什么?
-We're not at risk.  -What are you talking about?
-我看到粉末飘出来  -它是无害的 杰克
-I watched the powder get out.  -It's harmless, Jack.
呈硅酸盐状 仅此而已
Some form of silicate, but that's all.
-啊?  -白粉中没有病毒
-What?  -There is no virus in the powder.
我们检验了五份样本 一点痕量都没有
We tested five Samples. There weren't even trace amounts.
空气和体表分析都呈阴性
Atmospheric and surface analysis also came up negative,
凯尔父母也呈阴性
and Kyle's parents tested negative, as well.
你确定?
You're sure about this?
我唯一不确定的是 我们是否找到了正确线索
The only thing I'm not sure about is if we're on the right trail.
不 抛在卫生部外的尸体与凯尔 辛格勒有关
No. No, the body that was dropped off at Health Services was linked to Kyle Singer.
萨拉扎怎么可能付钱让他运送 一包没用的白粉?
Why would Salazar's people pay him to bring across a bag of worthless powder?
杰克 那我们该从何处着手?
Fine, Jack, but where do we even start looking?
不知道
I don't know.
等等
Wait a second.
马切尔说毒品只可能以晶体形态被运送 是吗?
Macer said the only way to transport the virus was in crystalline form, right?
对 这是病毒离开人体 唯一能存活的形态
Yeah, that's the only way it can survive outside a living body.
也许病毒根本没有离开人体呢?
What if it was never outside a living body?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
要是病毒被携带在活人身上呢?
What if the virus was transported in a living host?
要是凯尔 辛格勒今早离开墨西哥前就被感染了呢?
What if Kyle Singer was infected earlier this morning in Mexico before he even left?
但萨拉扎无法左右辛格勒的行动 到处传染人呢
But Salazar has no leverage if Singer was walking around, infecting people.
问题就在这 他还没有传染性
That's the point. He wouldn't be contagious yet.
潜伏期有14小时
The incubation period is 14 hours.
对 想一想
Right. Think about it.
我们知道凯尔 辛格勒 11小时前在墨西哥
We know for a fact that Kyle Singer was in Mexico 11 hours ago.
赫克托 萨拉扎威胁3小时后散播病毒
Hector Salazar hasn't threatened to release the virus for another three hours.
加起来正好
The math adds up.
我们得找到凯尔 辛格勒
We need to find Kyle Singer.
-喂?  -琳达.
-Hello?  -Linda.
凯尔 我们没什么好说的了
Kyle, I told you, I have nothing to say to you.
不 听我说 好吗?
No, listen to me, okay?
-我有麻烦  -当然 因为你在做毒品交易
-I'm in trouble.  -Yeah, because you're dealing drugs.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
出什么事了?
What happened?
我爸发现了白粉
My dad found the stuff.
我们大吵一架
We got in a fight,
我们发生了争抢 货被我爸抢去了
I split, but he's still got it, okay?
我得把货交给那些人 懂吗?
And I got to get this them, all right?
那些人可不好对付 我得把事情搞定
These guys are hard core. I got to make it right.
搞定? 怎么做?
Make it right? How?
我想 也许
I know, I was thinking, you know, maybe,
还钱给他们 也许
maybe I could pay them enough, you know, just
-他们就不再骚扰我  -你想让我给你钱?
-to keep them off my back. -You want me to give you money?
不 不 只是借
No, no, no, just borrow.
借多少?
How much?
两万美元 我在街上
It's about 20 grand on the street.
我没那么多钱 凯尔
I don't have that kind of money, Kyle.
你不是说你爸在家有些现金吗?
Didn't you say your dad keeps some cash around the house?
-没那么多  -琳达 听我说!
-Not that much.  -Linda, listen to me!
那些人...
These guys...
如果我拿不出东西 他们会杀了我
they will kill me if I don't give them something.
求你了... 多少帮点忙
Please... please, anything will help right now.
你想让我也卷进去?
Now you want me to get involved in this?
就... 求你借点给我 多少都行
Just... please let me borrow something, anything.
我会还你的 我发誓
I'll pay you back, I swear to god.
-你在哪儿?  -商场外
-Where are you?  -I'm at the mall.
-我尽快过去  -谢谢
-I'll get there as soon as I can.  -Thank you.
反恐局已知道白粉只是幌子 他们正在找辛格勒
CTU knows the powder is not real. Now they're going after Singer.
想要我怎么做?
What do you want me to do?
跟着他 没人的时候
Stay with him, and as soon as he's alone,
-抓住他控制他  -是
-Grab him and take him into containment.  -Done.
别让警察捉住他
You can't let the cops get him.
没有辛格勒 就没用了
We need Singer to make this work.
当然释放萨拉扎是不可能的
Of course there's no way we'll ever release Salazar.
反恐局很快就能掌控局面
CTU is very close to containing the threat.
嗯 对
Yes, that's right.
好的 斯坦
All right, Stan.
有消息我会通知你
I'll make sure you're kept in the loop.
有新情况吗 韦恩?
What have we got, Wayne?
我同安妮的前夫谈过了
I just talked to Anne's ex-husband.
听着 泰德 帕卡德想要的只是钱
Now, listen, all Ted Packard wants is money.
如果我们肯付钱 他就撤消陈述
If we pay him off, he'll recant before this debate.
这是敲诈
That's blackmail.
-这是交易  -我不觉得
-That's business.  -I don't think so.
大卫 比起去反驳对你不利的陈述
David, it's a hell of a lot cheaper than trying to defend against this allegation,
这可要便宜得多
which is going to hurt you.
我勇于面对这些谎言
I've faced down worse lies.
我们的公信度还可以
I think I've earned some credibility.
看了今早的民意调查没有?
You read the polls this morning?
基勒的支持率 逼近我们
Because Keeler is closing the gap,
竞选又提前了
and this race is much closer than it should be.
听着 虽然这事令人不快 但
And listen, I know it's distasteful there, but
以成本角度上 非常划算
in cost-benefit terms, it's a no brainer.
安妮不会这样以为
Anne won't think so.
-安妮不用知道  -我不会对她隐瞒
-Anne doesn't have to know.  -I can't keep it from her.
好 这是你选的
Well, that's your choice.
这事抖了出来
But if this comes out,
安妮就要上全国各大报纸的头条
Anne is going to find herself on the front page of every single newspaper in this country,
大卫 她不是雪莉 她经不起那样的审视
and David, she's not Sherry. She's not equipped to handle that kind of scrutiny,
你也没办法保护她
and you will not be able to protect her from it.
在辩论和事件爆发之间
Now, between this debate
你有足够时间考虑你的选择
and the threat of this outbreak, you have enough on your plate to worry about.
别当殉道者
Don't be a martyr.
大事化小 小事化了
Keep it simple.
我们一小时内能弄到钱
We could have the money within the hour.
好吧
Do it.
怎么了?
What's going on?
他们脱下了隔离服 就是说我们安全了?
They don't have their suits on. What does that mean? Are we okay?
对 白粉没有病毒
Yes. The powder was harmless.
-感谢上帝...  -你无缘无故这样对待我们
-Oh, thank god...  -Then you put us through all this for nothing.
-把我们吓个半死  -辛格勒先生 我们还要找你儿子
-You scared the hell out of us.  -Mr. Singer, we still need to find your son.
有没有线索 能帮我们找到他?
Is there anything that you can tell us that would help?
干嘛? 不是说白粉没有病毒了吗
Why? You just said the powder was harmless.
我们相信你儿子今早在墨西哥 感染了病毒
We believe that your son was infected with the virus in Mexico earlier this morning
在他回家前
before he came home.
在他具有传染性前 我们只有3小时找他
We have three hours to find him before he becomes contagious.
你说什么
What are you saying,
我们儿子会死?
that our son could die?
-对 有可能  -噢 上帝
-Yes, that could happen.  -Oh, god.
我知道你们很难过 对不起
I know how difficult this must be for you, and I'm sorry.
但我们必须找到他 马上
But we need to find your son, we need to find him now.
-打过他手机吗?  -嗯 打不通
-Have you tried his cell phone?  -Yes. The line's been disconnected.
呃 等等
No, wait. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
等等
Wait.
-他早上拿走了我的电话  -号码多少?
-He took my phone this morning.  -What's the number?
818-555-0103.
818-555-0103
很好
Okay.
你俩中找个人给他说
I'm going to need one of you to call him.
都是我的错
This is my fault.
我没照顾好这个家 我没资格跟他说
I never would have done any of this if I couldn't take care of my own family.
-不  -你知道 这是真的
-No.  -Yes. You know, it's true.
托尼 我是杰克
Tony, it's Jack.
杰克 我已通知警局 他们正全境抓捕辛格勒
Yeah, Jack, I just spoke to LAPD. They've got a priority APB on Singer.
很好 我们找到了他的联系电话
Okay, good. I think we've got a number on him.
很好
All right, look,
马上对号码进行跟踪
we'll thread the line through a tracing matrix.
好 号码是818-555-0103
Okay. The number is 818-555-0103.
把此号的线路 转到我手机上
I want you to route the call back to my cell phone.
好的
You got it.
跟踪此号码 并将线路转到杰克手机上
I want you to trace that number and reroute the call to Jack's cell phone.
你们谁来打电话
I'm going to need one of you to make the call now,
尽量拖延通话时间 以便我们追踪他
I need you to keep him on the line as long as possible so we can trace him.
我该跟他说什么?
What am I supposed to tell him?
事实
The truth.
托尼 设好了吗?
Tony, you set?
嗯 就绪
Yeah, we're ready.
-琳达  -凯尔 我是爸爸
-Linda.  -Kyle, it's your father.
爸?
Dad?
我们谈谈
We need to talk.
我不知道你想谈什么
Look, I don't know what you want to talk about.
我很讨厌你 知道吗?
I already know how pissed off you are, okay?
听着 嗯
Look, um,
不管你做了什么...
whatever you did...
我知道你是想帮助我和你妈
I know you were just trying to help out your mom and me.
哦 除非你肯把东西还给我
Yeah, well, look, unless you're willing to give back the stuff you took,
我才能把事情搞定 好吗?
I got to deal with the situation, okay?
凯尔! 拜托别挂电话
Kyle! Please, don't hang up.
拜托! 听我说
Please! Listen.
听我说
Listen to me.
我有重要的事告诉你 拜托
What I'm telling you is important. Please,
你必须回家一趟
you have to come home.
爸 你声音怎么有点奇怪?
Dad, why do you sound different?
你要相信我告诉你的事
I need you to trust me on something I'm about to tell you.
爸?
Dad?
你可能感染了病毒
You may have gotten a virus,
在墨西哥的时候
something you picked up in Mexico.
你怎么知道我去了墨西哥?
How'd you know I went to Mexico?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
但你可能身染重疾
But you may be sick.
如果是真的 你得去看医生
And if you are, then you need to get checked out by a doctor.
爸 我不知你在说什么?
Dad, I don't know what you're talking about, all right?
-我很好  -我知道这听起来很疯狂
-But I feel fine.  -I know it sounds crazy,
但却是真的
but it's real.
这里有人想帮助你
Now, there's e some people here who are trying to help.
-警察?  -不是
-Cops?  -No
托尼 跟踪到电话了吗?
Tony, have you got a lock on this trace?
-这孩子快挂电话了  -还要多久?
-We're going to lose this kid.  -How much longer?
我查了信号塔 在半径三英里范围内
I've got the cell tower, but it's covering a three-mile radius.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
太矛盾了 刚在说你们爱我
This fight, one minute you tell me that you love me,
下一秒又把我出卖给警察
the next minute, you're selling me out to some cops.
他们不是警察 凯尔
They're not police, Kyle.
他们只是在阻止病毒扩散
They're just trying to stop this virus before it becomes an outbreak.
爸 我说了感觉很好 好吗?
Dad, I already told you I feel fine, all right?
他们说你几小时后 会出现病症
They're saying that you're not going to start feeling sick for another few hours.
-但到那时 就太迟了  -托尼 锁定位置了吗?
-But by then, it's going to be too late.  -Tony, have you got a lock yet?
还要多久?
How much longer?
十秒
10 seconds.
你想让我干嘛? 去自首?
What do you want me to do? You want me to turn myself in?
因为你可能病了
Because you may be sick.
如果是真的 其它人也会被感染
And if you are, other people are going to get infected.
-托尼...  -查到了 杰克
-Tony...  -We got it, Jack.
他在洛斯费利兹商场 佛蒙特和日落街之间
He's at the Los Feliz Mall, between Vermont and Sunset.
把他的照片发给商场保安
Okay, get his photograph over to mall security.
叫他们别接近他
Tell them not to approach him.
杰克,
Jack
你开车去那儿要20分钟 我10分钟内在那儿布置队伍
you're 20 minutes away by car, I can land a team there in ten minutes.
好
Fine.
托尼 别派蔡斯
Tony, I don't want you taking Chase.
-为什么?  -照我说的做
-Why not?  -I just don't.
谢谢你们
Thank you very much.
如果我们抓到了他 就通知你们
We'll notify you as soon as we have him in custody.
求你了 帮帮他
Please, help our son.
我们会的
We will.
奥布莱恩.
O'Brian
克萝伊 不知你听见了吗 托尼要马上出动
Chloe, I'm not sure you've heard yet, But Tony's heading off site for a while.
是吗?
He is?
嗯 接下来几小时由我负责
Yeah. I'm taking over for a few hours.
-好  -通知你那个部门的人
-Okay.  -Let people in your area know.
-好的  -谢谢
-Okay, I will.  -Thanks.
什么事?
What was that?
是米歇尔 她会掌管反恐小组几小时
Michelle. She's taking over CTU for a couple of hours.
托尼呢?
Where's Tony?
他们找出了辛格勒所在处
They have a location on Singer.
杰克无法及时赶到 托尼就去了
Jack can't get there in time, so Tony's going.
啊? 托尼又不是外勤组的
What? Tony's not field ops.
看来他们已有所行动 但将你排除在外
Seems like they're really going out of their way to cut you out of the loop.
你做了让杰克讨厌的事?
Did you do something to piss off Jack?
别这样 蔡斯 只会让事情更糟
Bad idea, Chase. You're just going to make things worse.
托尼...
Tony...
我听说找到了凯尔 辛格勒 是真的吗?
I just heard they found Kyle Singer. Is this for real?
去了就知 我会和杰克在那儿碰头
We'll see. I'm meeting Jack over there right now.
听着 帕克审讯完毕 该招的都招了
Look, I'm done with this kid Parker. He's said all he's gonna say.
-我想跟这案子  -好啦
-I want back on the case.  -Yeah, well,
让我们来处理 蔡斯 好吗?
we're handling it now, Chase, all right?
是杰克不想我参与吗?
Because Jack doesn't want me there, right?
他说了排挤我的理由吗?
Did he tell you why he's cutting me out?
我没兴趣 他是你上级 这是他的命令
I don't really care. He's your boss, it's his call.
这不公平
This isn't right.
他说是因为金吗?
Did he tell you this is because of Kim?
他知道我们在交往 他要我为此付出代价
He found out we were seeing each other, and this is how he's going to make me pay for it.
留着跟杰克谈吧
Take it up with Jack.
我想把线路留给托尼
Just want to keep the line open for Tony.
给杰克·鲍尔留言
Leave a message for Jack Bauer.
见鬼 杰克
Damn it, Jack.
蔡斯.
Chase
我知道我爸很生气 但他会消气的
Look, I know my dad can be hard, but he will come around.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
因为我了解他
Because I know my father.
也许你并没有你想的那么了解他
Maybe you don't know him as well as you think.
你这是什么意思?
What is that supposed to mean?
没什么
Nothing.
没事了 金
It's okay. Forget it, Kim.
不觉得我已经够烦了吗?
Don't you think I feel bad enough already?
我很烦
Because I do.
我们不应该告诉他
We shouldn't have told him.
我们还有另外一个办法 就是停止交往
Well, the only other option I can think of is for us to stop seeing each other,
但这不在我考虑范围内
which as far as I'm concerned, is not an option.
或者我应该考虑?
Or is it?
-蔡斯 你有什么想法?  -我想做回我的工作
-Chase, what do you want?  -I want to be able to do my job.
金 快回工作岗位 托尼要到了
Kim, we need you at your station. Tony's about to land.
托尼·阿尔梅达 反恐小组
Tony Almeida, CTU.
我们找到了你们要的人
I think we found the guy you're looking for.
他在大厅
He's in the rotunda.
-布朗森 看住东出口  -是
-Bronson, lock down the east exit.  -Yes, sir.
皮尔森 你去保安办公室
Pierson, I want you to run point from the security office.
好
Alright.
你吸毒多久了 杰克?
How long have you been using, Jack?
什么?
What?
我做过康复培训 能辨别出吸毒的人
I did a rotation in rehab. You learn to pick out when someone's using.
-不知道你在说什么  -你知道
-I don't know what you're talking about.  -You know exactly what I'm talking about.
多久了?
How long?
有一阵了
For a while now.
只有这样做才能瞒过萨拉扎
It was the only way I could maintain my cover with the Salazars.
-现在很兴奋?  -不
-Are you high now?  -No.
-这个空了 杰克  -妮可 我没事
-It's empty, Jack.  -Nicole, I told you I'm fine.
-我看未必  -那你去打我的报告啊
-I'm not so sure.  -If you're not so sure, then turn me in.
我不想打你的报告 杰克
I don't want to turn you in, Jack.
我担心你
I'm worried about you.
不用 我已经戒了
You don't have to be. I've kicked it.
我有责任控制病毒
I have a responsibility to stop this virus,
比你这些阻碍 我相信你能发挥更大作用
and I am taking a calculated risk that you are more of an asset than a liability.
别把事情搞砸了
Just please don't screw this up.
不会的
I won't.
-喂?  -喂 杰克
-Yeah?  -Hey, Jack,
保安发现了辛格勒 我马上去逮捕他
Security found Singer. I'm about to pick him up.
很好 你在哪儿?
Okay, where are you?
二楼大厅 北扶梯口
Second floor rotunda, top of the north escalator.
你呢?
Where are you?
快到北门入口了
We're coming into the loading dock, north entrance.
-你看到他了吗?  -看到了
-Have you got a visual?  -Yeah, I got him.
-你有人布置在哪儿?  -各个主要出入口
-Where have you placed your men?  -We posted at all the main entrances.
很好 一分钟后见
Okay, good. We should be there in a minute.
好
All right.
让你的人在停车场各出入口待命
Have your men cover all the parking level exits.
我们上!
Let's go!
我不想引起任何骚乱
I don't want to cause any kind of commotion.
-喂?  -反恐小组在这儿
-Yeah?  -CTU's here.
他们打算对那孩子采取行动
They're about to move in on the kid.
先别行动 很棘手
Just stand down. It's too hot.
这是我唯一的机会 我不能让男孩被抓走
This is my only chance. We can't let the kid get caught.
-别 别 等一下  -我不能等 戈麦斯!
-No, no, wait.  -I can't wait. Gomez!
你在这儿等 我正大光明地去抓他
Wait here, I want to make a clean grab.
是
Yes, sir.
凯尔.
Kyle
你是谁?
Who are you?
我叫托尼·阿尔梅达
My name's Tony Almeida.
我是联邦探员 来帮你的
I'm a federal agent, but I'm here to help you.
你爸说你病了 是真的
What your father told you about your being sick is true.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
跟我来 我证明给你看
You come with me, I'll prove it to you.
快让开! 行动!
Get out of the way! Move!
妮可 他的颈部被击中了!
Nicole, he's been hit in the neck!
杰米 给我对讲机
Jamie, give me your walkie-talkie.
我们的警官被击中了
We have an officer down.
凯尔 辛格勒逃了 重复 凯尔 辛格勒逃了
Kyle Singer is not in custody. I repeat, Kyle Singer is not in custody.
各出口注意警戒
Maintain cover on all exits.